<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<resources>

    <string name="app_name">Spring Android</string>

    <string name="text_main">Select an option to view the associated example.</string>

    <string name="text_http_get_description">These examples make HTTP GET requests to the server.</string>

    <string name="text_http_get_json_xml_description">These examples retrieve a list of states from the
        example server. Use the MappingJacksonHttpMessageConverter to marshal JSON objects or use
        the SimpleXmlHttpMessageConverter to marshal XML objects via HTTP GET requests.
    </string>

    <string name="text_http_get_google_search_description">Two examples of Google searches, where the first
        marshals JSON using Jackson, and the second uses the Google Gson parser.
    </string>

    <string name="text_http_get_gzip_description">These examples illustrate the use of gzip
        compression with an HTTP GET request. You can view the response headers to compare the
        Content-Encoding, and Content-Size for the compressed versus uncompressed responses.
    </string>

    <string name="text_http_get_parameters_description">These examples pass a parameter to the
        RestTemplate instance to retrieve a state by its abbreviation. Use the
        MappingJacksonHttpMessageConverter to marshal JSON objects or use the
        SimpleXmlHttpMessageConverter to marshal XML objects via HTTP GET requests.
    </string>

    <string name="text_http_get_set_request_timeout_description">The HttpComponents Http Client has
        the option of setting a timeout when making http requests. This examples shows how to set the timeout
        when attempting to make a request to the example server. The server delay value will cause the server
        to delay its response for that many seconds. The request timeout will cause the request to timeout after
        the specified number of seconds.
    </string>

    <string name="text_http_post_description">These examples make HTTP POST requests to the server.</string>

    <string name="text_rss_description">These examples retrieve the RSS feed from blog.springsource.com.
        RSS feeds can be retrieved with the SyndFeedHttpMessageConverter or the more specific
        RssChannelHttpMessageConverter. The SyndFeed message converter supports RSS and ATOM using an
        abstracted object model.
    </string>

    <string name="text_atom_description">These examples retrieve the ATOM feed from
        jira.springframework.org. ATOM feeds can be retrieved with the SyndFeedHttpMessageConverter
        or the more specific AtomFeedHttpMessageConverter. The SyndFeed message converter supports
        RSS and ATOM using an abstracted object model.
    </string>

    <string name="twitter_description">Twitter example using Spring Social.</string>

    <string name="facebook_description">Facebook example using Spring Social</string>

    <string-array name="main_menu_items">
        <item>HTTP GET</item>
        <item>HTTP POST</item>
        <item>Twitter</item>
        <item>Facebook</item>
    </string-array>

    <string-array name="http_get_activity_menu_items">
        <item>JSON and XML</item>
        <item>Sending parameters</item>
        <item>Google Search</item>
        <item>Requesting gzip content</item>
        <item>Setting a Request Timeout</item>
    </string-array>

    <string-array name="http_get_json_xml_activity_menu_items">
        <item>Fetch JSON list of states</item>
        <item>Fetch XML list of states</item>
    </string-array>

    <string-array name="http_get_google_search_menu_items">
        <item>Google Search with Jackson</item>
        <item>Google Search with Gson</item>
    </string-array>

    <string-array name="http_get_gzip_activity_menu_items">
        <item>Compressed String</item>
        <item>Uncompressed String</item>
        <item>Compressed JSON</item>
    </string-array>

    <string-array name="http_post_activity_options">
        <item>String</item>
        <item>JSON and XML</item>
        <item>MultiValueMap</item>
        <item>Form Data</item>
    </string-array>

</resources>
